{"data":[{"question":"Well, I think that the prices here are ________.","a":"reason","b":"reasonable","c":"reasonably","d":"a reason","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To be + adj.\u00a0\n- Reasonable= fair\/acceptable.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you feel ________ to this kind of job?","a":"attractive","b":"attracted","c":"attraction","d":"attract","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Feel\/smell\/ taste...+ adj.\u00a0\n- Someone feel attracted to sth.\u00a0\n- Something is attractive to sbd.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"American women ________ independent.","a":"are used to be","b":"are used to being","c":"is used to being","d":"is used to be","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb-ing: be familiar with sth.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Which would you ________, tea or coffee?","a":"preference","b":"preferential","c":"prefer","d":"preferable","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Sentence structure: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"They are ________ doing the same thing every day.","a":"bored with","b":"fond of","c":"afraid of","d":"like","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Doing the same thing that often leads to boredom.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Ask the shop ________ where the washing powder is.","a":"nurse","b":"assistant","c":"barber","d":"conductor","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Shop assistant: the sale-person in shop.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"That ________ sells very good meat.","a":"baker","b":"dentist","c":"architect","d":"butcher","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Butcher: person who sells meat.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"If my tooth doesn't stop hurting. I'll go and see my ________.","a":"actor","b":"dentist","c":"writer","d":"jockey","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Dentist: a doctor who cares of tooth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Not many buses have a ________ You usually pay the driver.","a":"manager","b":"farmer","c":"conductor","d":"porter","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conductor: someone who collect payment from passenger on a bus.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Look! The ________ is feeding the lions.","a":"keeper","b":"pianist","c":"postman","d":"engineer","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Keeper: someone who looks after animals.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"}]}